Robert S. Griffin Jr. 113 Ethridge St. Battleboro , NC 27809 Cell (252) 343-9629

Email RSGJR1980@yahoo.com

Education: (July 02') GED, Nash Community College

Summary of Qualifications:

Machine operations, various measuring devices (indication, dial, flush, pin gages) Experienced in plumbing using various tools for trade to complete job/task.

Experienced Customer service skills

Experienced in warehousing, inventory control including: truck loading, receiving, inspection, stock rotation, and cycle counting, Phone/fax, Communicating messages between groups of people, Quality control, Safety procedures, filing liability reports, theft report, auto accident reports, and safety violation reports.

Certified operator of material handling equipment including: hand pallet trucks, electric pallet jacks, walkie stacker, rider pallet trucks, stock pickers, cherry pickers, and stand up forklifts, LP forklifts, bob cat stick steers, grappling cranes, front end loaders, ditch witches and other various light to heavy machinery. Strick usuage of safety guidelines and use of PPE's. Experienced in retail sales.

Work Experiences:

CUMMINS, Whitakers, NC From: 04/2015- 02/2019 Position: Machine technician

Duties: Set up , run , various machinery in a mass manufacturing facility of diesel engines. Responsible for scheduled/unscheduled tool changes. Quality inspection on engines using various hand gages and other measuring devices to insure product meets strict engineering guidelines. Worked with other supporting staff (engineering, Gage lab, maintenance, quality) to fix , update machinery for production needs.

Holden Temporaries inc. Rocky Mount, NC

From: 03/2014-12/2014

Position: Kiln fireman/Operator & Maintenance Tec.

Duties: Operate brick kiln using sawdust and natural gas in a timely and safe manner. As well as

maintain plant and facility machinery through preventative maintenance and unscheduled break downs.

Manpower, Wilson, NC / Rocky Mount, NC

From: 02/2014-04/2015

Position: Package operator, assembly technician.

Duties: Packaged product for pharmaceutical company using packaging line equipment.

Installed various diesel components onto engines.

Griffin's Plumbing Company, Whitakers, NC

present - 1/1998

Position: Plumbing specialist

Duties:Installed and repair plumbing fixtures. In new/repair work in residential homes. installed or repaired water lines. tested all new and repaired installation for leaks and proper functions. located and repaired water line leaks. used various power tools (wrenches, sockets,drills,etc.) used electrical skills to hook up or disconnect power or replace electrical plumbing units.

LOWE'S Home Centers Inc, Goldsboro, NC

From: 2/2005 – 4/2006 Position: Plumbing specialist

Duties:Was responsible for department sales, installed sales including customer contracts dealing with paying and installation of LOWE'S products, product stocking using provided equipment and safety equipment, Product location updates, Assisting customers on phone and or in person with product questions and installations, Help resolve customer complaints about products or product installs.

Holden Temporaries Inc, Goldsboro, NC

From: 1/2005 - 2 /2005

Position: Security officer/ furniture deliverer

Duties: Worked for temp. agency doing security on bank construction grounds overnight and during day delivered furniture as temp employee for Furniture Fair. Duties included Pulling delivery orders out of stock and delivering them to customers. As well as stay on grounds overnight at a bank construction site making sure suspicious activities were reported to proper authorities.

Atlantic Scrap & Processing LL, Smithfield, NC

From: 6/2004 - 1/2005

Position: Heavy machinery operator

Duties: Operated A Shear machine cutting oversized steel pieces into three foot sections for rail cars. Operated a grappling crane to load and unload tractor trailers of cars, white goods, and other steel products to be inspected for hazardous products not allowed to be recycled. Loaded the recycling belt at steel recycling facility with cars and white goods. Used a front end loader to move, clean pathways, and unload steel recyclables. Operated bob cats and forklifts to achieve my goals of production as well.

Precision Airflow, Smithfield, NC

From:02/2004 - 6 /2004

Position: Temporary employee machine operator/ material handler

Duties: Using a pneumatic pressing machine to lock air filter assembly permanently into place, used heated wire sealer machine to inclose filters into shipping bags, boxed for shipping as well as used forklifts to load stock for shipping. Pulled materials for air filter assembly lines depending on the days demands.

Kelly Services, Rocky Mount/Wilson, NC

From:1/2004 - 2 /2004

Position: Temporary employee as Security officer/ Stocker

Duties: Performed security duties at MERK Pharmaceutical company. Worked at Pepsi Co as a

third shift truck stocker.

Cox Target Media, Elm City, NC

From:6/2003 - 12/2003 Position: Machine Operator

Duties: Set up and run a pneumatic machine that filled envelopes with coupons to be mailed by

mass marketing firm.